{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822288578","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822288578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" aad29471-0b8b-4323-8644-9b57c95e25f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822291559","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822291559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" aad29471-0b8b-4323-8644-9b57c95e25f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822291624","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822291623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" aad29471-0b8b-4323-8644-9b57c95e25f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822299405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822299405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" aad29471-0b8b-4323-8644-9b57c95e25f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822315216","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822315216"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" e2bb223e-5026-406c-91b8-d9402516ed6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822315441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822315440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" e2bb223e-5026-406c-91b8-d9402516ed6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822316404","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822316404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" e2bb223e-5026-406c-91b8-d9402516ed6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822317678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822317678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" e2bb223e-5026-406c-91b8-d9402516ed6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822319283","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822319282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" e2bb223e-5026-406c-91b8-d9402516ed6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822319371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822319371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" e2bb223e-5026-406c-91b8-d9402516ed6c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822333507","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822333507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822334145","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822334144"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822334385","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822334385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822334911","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822334911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822336261","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822336260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822336493","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822336492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822336994","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822336993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822338019","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822338019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822339073","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822339073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" AKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822340103","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822340102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" KICHAKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822348337","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822348337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822354224","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822354224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822355680","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822355680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822364855","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822364855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822366355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822366355"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822368456","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822368456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822370401","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822370401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822372126","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822372126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822374033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822374033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822376575","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822376575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822379628","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822379628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822392477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822392477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822394298","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822394297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822395561","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822395561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" ALIKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822395755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822395755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822396318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822396318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822399034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822399034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822401217","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822401217"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822406032","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822406032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822407113","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822407113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822408827","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822408827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822411636","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822411635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822412329","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822412329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822413782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822413782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" AKIPUMZIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822414326","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822414326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822414779","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822414778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822415452","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822415452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822415966","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822415966"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822416680","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822416680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSIMU"," userResponse":" MSIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822416794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822416794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822417548","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822417548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822423734","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822423734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822424487","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822424487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822427867","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822427866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822428843","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822428843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822430577","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822430577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822434273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822434273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822449487","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822449487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822452253","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822452253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822454484","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822454484"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822456665","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822456665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822464406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822464406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822466445","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822466445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822466724","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822466724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSIMU"," userResponse":" MSIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822466936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822466936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822470346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822470346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822473082","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822473082"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUTANO"," userResponse":" MAKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822473738","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822473737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822474837","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822474836"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALITOKEA"," userResponse":" YALITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822475487","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822475487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822476323","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822476323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822476846","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822476846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822477457","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822477456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIJUE"," userResponse":" ASIJUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822477625","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822477625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822478308","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822478308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822481238","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822481238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUTANO"," userResponse":" MAKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822486168","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822486168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822488082","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822488082"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YALITOKEA"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822489544","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822489544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YALITOKEA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822491277","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822491277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALITOKEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822493265","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822493265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822496760","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822496760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822498577","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822498576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822501650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822501649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822503230","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822503230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822504717","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822504717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASIJUE"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822508355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822508355"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASIJUE"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822510465","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822510464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIJUE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822511357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822511357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822511430","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822511430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" START_KUFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822513874","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822513874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822516223","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822516221"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJAWA"," userResponse":" ALIJAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822516492","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822516492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822517200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822517199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOGA"," userResponse":" WOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822519023","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822519023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJAWA"," userResponse":" ALIJAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822526097","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822526097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822543567","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822543567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOGA"," userResponse":" WOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822546479","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822546479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822547304","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822547304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822548700","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822548700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHANGAA"," userResponse":" ALISHANGAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822549664","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822549664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822550231","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822550231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822551037","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822551037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPA"," userResponse":" KUOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822551688","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822551688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822555138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822555138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822557064","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822557064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822557939","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822557939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHANGAA"," userResponse":" START_ALISHANGAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822559161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822559161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHANGAA"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822561187","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822561186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHANGAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822563447","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822563447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822565863","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822565863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822567328","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822567327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822568990","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822568990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822574112","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822574111"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822586282","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822586282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPA"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822588522","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822588521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPA"," userResponse":" KUOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822588924","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822588924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822591019","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822591019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822592212","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822592212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNGURUMO"," userResponse":" MNGURUMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822592864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822592864"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822594171","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822594171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULISIKIKA"," userResponse":" ULISIKIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822594684","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822594683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822595348","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822595347"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" TUMBONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822595853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822595853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822596628","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822596628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822597486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822597485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822597751","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822597751"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822598792","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822598792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822620330","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822620329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822620752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822620752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MNGURUMO"," userResponse":" START_MNGURUMO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822622797","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822622797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNGURUMO"," userResponse":" MNGURUMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822626378","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822626378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822628919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822628919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULISIKIKA"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822651960","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822651960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULISIKIKA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822653837","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822653836"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULISIKIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822654741","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822654741"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822659251","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822659251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822660794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822660794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822662405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822662405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822663429","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822663429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822664898","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822664898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822667101","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822667101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822668940","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822668940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822669650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822669650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822671102","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822671102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822672600","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822672600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822673406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822673406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822676197","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822676197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822678435","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822678434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822678991","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822678990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822680130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822680130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIKUTA"," userResponse":" ALIJIKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822680626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822680625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822680782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822680782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822681343","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822681342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822681884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822681884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822683896","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822683896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822688621","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822688621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822691783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822691783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIKUTA"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIKUTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822695641","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822695640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIKUTA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822697694","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822697693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIKUTA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822700193","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822700192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822703467","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822703467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822705886","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822705886"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822705889","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822705889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822711621","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822711621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822713677","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822713676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822714518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822714517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPIGA"," userResponse":" KUPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822715257","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822715257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822719002","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822719001"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822721582","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822721582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822723459","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822723458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822724008","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822724008"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUPIGA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822725438","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822725438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUPIGA"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822726903","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822726902"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPIGA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822727199","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822727198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822730033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822730033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822732354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822732353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822733302","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822733301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" ALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822733897","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822733897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822733984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822733984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822734495","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822734494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822735612","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822735611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" AKISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822736179","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822736179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLO"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822742616","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822742616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822745783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822745783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822748490","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822748489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822749436","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822749435"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" ALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822749817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822749817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822751638","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822751637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822756099","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822756098"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822756933","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822756933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" AKISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822757008","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822757008"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLO"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822758721","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822758720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822759762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822759761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ULIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822760394","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822760393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822761318","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822761318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822762587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822762586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822763321","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822763320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822764601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822764600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" USINGIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822767311","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822767311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822768505","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822768505"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822769966","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822769966"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822771795","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822771795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822771954","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822771954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822775462","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822775462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822780653","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822780653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFANYA"," userResponse":" USINGIZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822788109","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822788109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFANYA"," userResponse":" START_ALIJIFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822789985","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822789985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFANYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822791063","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822791063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" START_SIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822794272","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822794272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822795829","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822795829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822798295","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822798295"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822800297","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822800296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822802384","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822802384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822804899","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822804898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822805010","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822805010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822805377","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822805377"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOROMOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOROMOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822805905","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822805905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822806307","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822806307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822806523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822806523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822806904","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822806903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWANGUKIA"," userResponse":" KUMWANGUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822807316","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822807316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822807762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822807761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822807795","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822807795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYELALA"," userResponse":" ALIYELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822813838","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822813837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822821855","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822821855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822822451","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822822451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822823171","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822823171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOROMOKA"," userResponse":" START_KUMWANGUKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822825804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822825804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOROMOKA"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822827685","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822827685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOROMOKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822832137","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822832137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822835444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822835444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822836423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822836423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822839048","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822839048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822843460","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822843460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWANGUKIA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822845091","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822845091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWANGUKIA"," userResponse":" KUMWANGUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822845667","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822845667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822847582","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822847582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" KUMWANGUKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822849218","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822849218"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" ALIYELALA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822850615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822850615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822852976","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822852976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYELALA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822856169","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822856169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYELALA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822858066","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822858066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYELALA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822859210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822859210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822860523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822860523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822861123","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822861123"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMKA"," userResponse":" WALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822861468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822861468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWA"," userResponse":" WAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822861666","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822861666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMECHANGANYIKIWA"," userResponse":" WAMECHANGANYIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822862199","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822862199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822862712","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822862712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPA"," userResponse":" KUOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822867441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822867441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822873821","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822873821"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMKA"," userResponse":" WALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822874652","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822874652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWA"," userResponse":" WAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822878873","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822878873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAMECHANGANYIKIWA"," userResponse":" WALIAMKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822880095","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822880095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAMECHANGANYIKIWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822882205","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822882205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMECHANGANYIKIWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822883439","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822883439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822887279","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822887278"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPA"," userResponse":" KUOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822889154","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822889154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822890138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822890138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISAHAU"," userResponse":" ALISAHAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822890581","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822890581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLO"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822891094","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822891094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822891708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822891708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822893361","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822893361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBILIA"," userResponse":" KUKIMBILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822894395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822894395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USALAMA"," userResponse":" USALAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822894818","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822894818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822897206","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822897206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" KUOGOPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822898816","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822898816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822900201","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822900201"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822901965","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822901965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALISAHAU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822903479","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822903478"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALISAHAU"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822905152","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822905152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISAHAU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822906389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822906389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLO"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822907619","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822907619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822909925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822909925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" START_KUKIMBILIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822911253","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822911253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822913898","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822913898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822913997","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822913996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBILIA"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822916403","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822916403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBILIA"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822918298","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822918298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBILIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822918758","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822918758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" USALAMA"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822924257","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822924257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" USALAMA"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822925825","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822925825"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USALAMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822932582","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822932582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822933613","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822933613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822935644","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822935644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822936248","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822936248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822937331","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822937331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822938285","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822938285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822939268","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822939268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" AKIELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822939801","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822939800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822940315","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822940314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822940478","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822940478"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822941022","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822941022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822943468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822943467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822943472","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822943472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822947368","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822947368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822949095","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822949095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822950957","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822950957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822951826","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822951826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822953208","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822953208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822954930","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822954930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822958562","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822958562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822960796","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822960796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822961067","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822961067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822962856","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822962856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822963574","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822963574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822966653","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822966653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822970942","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822970942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822971344","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822971344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822973545","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822973545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822974048","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822974048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822974853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822974853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822975726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822975726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" AKIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822975899","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822975899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822976402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822976402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822981575","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822981575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822984874","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822984874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822985807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822985807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822988916","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822988916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_KWAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822992146","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822992146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822993853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822993853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549822999392","data":{"timestamp":" 1549822999392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823003836","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823003836"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823005587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823005587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823007157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823007157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823009134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823009133"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823010966","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823010966"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823013513","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823013513"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823014876","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823014876"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823016783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823016783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823017276","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823017276"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823018340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823018340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBADILISHA"," userResponse":" ALIBADILISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823018954","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823018954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWELEKEO"," userResponse":" MWELEKEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823019567","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823019567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823020049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823020049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823020993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823020993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUEPUKA"," userResponse":" KUEPUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823021486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823021485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIWA"," userResponse":" KULIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823021649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823021649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823022123","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823022123"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823024285","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823024285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823024288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823024288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823026992","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823026991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBADILISHA"," userResponse":" START_ALIBADILISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823036325","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823036325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBADILISHA"," userResponse":" START_ALIBADILISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823038340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823038340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBADILISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823038504","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823038504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWELEKEO"," userResponse":" START_MWELEKEO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823045898","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823045898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MWELEKEO"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823047603","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823047602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWELEKEO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823051237","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823051237"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823053071","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823053071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823063525","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823063524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUEPUKA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823072275","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823072275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUEPUKA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823074010","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823074009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUEPUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823076189","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823076189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIWA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823078052","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823078052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIWA"," userResponse":" KULIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823079950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823079950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823081214","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823081214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823082448","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823082448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823083850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823083850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823085862","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823085861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823086032","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823086032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 888a6d57-fe92-451d-9224-f57da62a43e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823153032","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823153032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823153667","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823153667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823153906","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823153906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823154426","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823154425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823155771","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823155770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823156002","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823156001"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823156524","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823156524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823157540","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823157540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823158573","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823158573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" AKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823159606","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823159606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" KICHAKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823169169","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823169168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823171574","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823171574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823184287","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823184286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823184387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823184387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" d831f320-7a9a-4c8e-9776-5fed25fcaa1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823199022","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823199021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823199666","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823199666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823199907","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823199907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823200430","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823200430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823201780","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823201779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823202011","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823202010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823202510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823202510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823203535","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823203534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823204583","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823204583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" AKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823205614","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823205613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" KICHAKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823207122","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823207121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823214817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823214817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823218467","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823218467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823221571","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823221571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823223803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823223803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823226262","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823226262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823226266","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823226266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823228475","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823228475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823236779","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823236779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823238983","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823238983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823240829","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823240828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823242101","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823242101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" ALIKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823242300","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823242300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823242863","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823242863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823244970","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823244970"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823247289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823247289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823249618","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823249618"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823253197","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823253197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823254947","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823254947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823256568","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823256568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823259315","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823259315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823260016","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823260015"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823261485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823261485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" AKIPUMZIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823262038","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823262038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823262501","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823262501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823263184","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823263184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823263711","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823263710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823264435","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823264435"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSIMU"," userResponse":" MSIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823264559","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823264558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823265324","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823265323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823267034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823267034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823268414","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823268414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823270462","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823270462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823271953","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823271953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" START_AKIPUMZIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823273909","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823273908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823276234","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823276234"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823277922","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823277921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823280671","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823280671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823280675","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823280674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823280681","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823280681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823281452","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823281452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823282175","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823282175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSIMU"," userResponse":" MSIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823283276","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823283275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823283886","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823283886"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823286637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823286636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUTANO"," userResponse":" MAKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823287287","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823287287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823288384","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823288384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALITOKEA"," userResponse":" YALITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823289033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823289032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823289884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823289883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823290417","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823290417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823291028","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823291028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIJUE"," userResponse":" ASIJUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823291200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823291200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823291877","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823291877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823293800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823293800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUTANO"," userResponse":" MAKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823294181","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823294181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823296307","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823296307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALITOKEA"," userResponse":" YALITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823296310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823296310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823297314","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823297314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823297916","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823297916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823299348","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823299348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" ASIJUE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823300947","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823300947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823301732","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823301732"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASIJUE"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823303255","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823303255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASIJUE"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823305311","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823305311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIJUE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823306293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823306293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823307397","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823307397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823309702","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823309701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823312052","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823312052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJAWA"," userResponse":" ALIJAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823312313","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823312313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823313034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823313032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOGA"," userResponse":" WOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823315136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823315136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJAWA"," userResponse":" ALIJAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823315451","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823315451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823315851","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823315851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOGA"," userResponse":" WOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823318785","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823318784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823319591","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823319590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823320992","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823320992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHANGAA"," userResponse":" ALISHANGAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823321944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823321944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823322506","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823322506"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823323300","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823323300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPA"," userResponse":" KUOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823323954","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823323954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823329673","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823329673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823330274","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823330274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823330665","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823330664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHANGAA"," userResponse":" ALISHANGAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823343996","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823343996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823348762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823348762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823348765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823348765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823352945","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823352945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPA"," userResponse":" KUOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823353049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823353049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823355156","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823355156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823356330","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823356329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNGURUMO"," userResponse":" MNGURUMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823356973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823356973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823358259","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823358258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULISIKIKA"," userResponse":" ULISIKIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823358770","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823358770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823359433","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823359433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" TUMBONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823359939","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823359938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823360713","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823360713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823361559","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823361558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823361812","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823361812"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823362836","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823362835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823378323","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823378323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823387450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823387449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823387606","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823387606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 1fff3ab9-26a3-4819-af97-2f23f33fc007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823400734","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823400734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823401357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823401357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823401590","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823401590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823402103","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823402103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823403446","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823403446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823403675","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823403675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823404182","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823404181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823405210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823405209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823406262","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823406262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" AKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823407289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823407288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" KICHAKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823414559","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823414559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823414562","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823414562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823414570","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823414570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823429508","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823429508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823439831","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823439831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823446776","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823446776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823448030","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823448030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823449654","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823449653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823451709","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823451709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" START_NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823452495","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823452495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823455051","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823455051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823455813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823455813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823463423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823463423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823465195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823465194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823467121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823467120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823474414","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823474414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823476531","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823476531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823478562","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823478562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823479935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823479935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823485850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823485849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823487801","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823487801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823489627","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823489627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823490897","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823490897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" ALIKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823491104","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823491103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823491688","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823491688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823495937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823495937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823497247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823497245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823498797","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823498797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" START_ALIKUTANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823500781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823500780"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823500937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823500937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823503066","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823503066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823505006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823505006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823506409","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823506408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823509214","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823509214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823509907","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823509907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823511380","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823511380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" AKIPUMZIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823511945","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823511945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823512405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823512405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823513089","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823513089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823513613","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823513613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823514341","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823514341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSIMU"," userResponse":" MSIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823514460","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823514460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823515227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823515226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823517494","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823517494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823520202","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823520202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823522637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823522637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823524360","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823524360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823527816","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823527816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" AKIPUMZIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823530858","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823530858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" MSIMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823532382","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823532382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823534194","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823534192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823535153","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823535153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823535956","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823535956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823537491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823537490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823542960","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823542959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823543280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823543280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823543284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823543283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSIMU"," userResponse":" MSIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823544434","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823544434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823545240","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823545240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823547943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823547942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUTANO"," userResponse":" MAKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823548598","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823548595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823549692","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823549692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALITOKEA"," userResponse":" YALITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823550325","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823550325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823550675","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823550675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823550777","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823550777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 4f9d74e4-84bd-4b55-8991-c63873a5b882"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823565449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823565449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 8c371fc9-20db-41d7-b378-68908b818ff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823569956","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823569956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 8c371fc9-20db-41d7-b378-68908b818ff8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823580768","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823580768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 7bfbb353-636c-44ca-aa38-adbb364d37e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rutu_rutu-gubo-zadi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rutu"," userResponse":" rutu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823583951","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823583951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 7bfbb353-636c-44ca-aa38-adbb364d37e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_rutu_rutu-gubo-zadi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823596525","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823596525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 3b1f345d-5237-4cd8-8d50-55b8a41827c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rutu_rutu-gubo-zadi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rutu"," userResponse":" rutu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823601605","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823601604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 3b1f345d-5237-4cd8-8d50-55b8a41827c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lera_pogu-lera-zeti"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lera"," userResponse":" lera"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549823605634","data":{"timestamp":" 1549823605634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_211116"," gameId":" 3b1f345d-5237-4cd8-8d50-55b8a41827c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_lera_pogu-lera-zeti"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}